let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Resultado de 1 x 3:",
        answer: "C. 3",
        Options: [
            "A. 1",
            "B. 2",
            "C. 3",
            "D. 5"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Resultado de 2 x 4:",
        answer: "B. 8",
        Options: [
            "A. 6",
            "B. 8",
            "C. 10", 
            "D. 12"        
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Resultado de 3 x 9:",
        answer: "B. 27",
        Options: [
            "A. 12", 
            "B. 27",
            "C. 18", 
            "D. 36"      
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Resultado de 4 x 5:",
        answer: "D. 20",
        Options: [
            "A. 10", 
            "B. 16",
            "C. 25", 
            "D. 20"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Resultado de 5 x 7:",
        answer: "A. 35",
        Options: [
            "A. 35", 
            "B. 42", 
            "C. 28", 
            "D. 50"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Resultado de 6 x 2:",
        answer: "C. 12",
        Options: [
            "A. 8", 
            "B. 14", 
            "C. 12", 
            "D. 16"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Resultado de 7 x 8:",
        answer: "A. 56",
        Options: [
            "A. 56", 
            "B. 64", 
            "C. 42", 
            "D. 49"   
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Resultado de 8 x 6:",
        answer: "A. 48",
        Options: [
            "A. 48", 
            "B. 36",
            "C. 54", 
            "D. 64"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Resultado de 9 x 9:",
        answer: "D. 81",
        Options: [
            "A. 54", 
            "B. 63", 
            "C. 72",
            "D. 81"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Resultado de 10 x 4:",
        answer: "B. 40",
        Options: [
            "A. 36", 
            "B. 40", 
            "C. 45", 
            "D. 50"
        ]
    }
];
